A Guide to the General Records of the University of Virginia Family Housing Association, 1966-1977
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
General Records of the University of Virginia Family Housing Association 1966-1977
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/42/1.801
This collection consists of ca. 600 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1980 February 15.
Scope and Content Information
General records of the Family Housing Association, a student organization concerned with married student housing at the University.
Contents List
- Complaints 1965-1975 (Box 1)
- Council Members 1967-1968 (Box 1)
- Disciplinary Problems and Trials 1968 (Box 1)
- Discount Information and VISA (Varsity International Sales Association) 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Election Information 1966-1977 (Box 1)
- Family Housing Council: Minutes 1967-1973 (Box 1)
- Family Housing Council: Mike Montgomery President for [1969-1970] 1968-1969 (Box 1)
- Family Housing Council: Len Murphy President for 1972-1973 1971-1976 (Box 1)
- Family Housing Council: Charles Reiss President for 1973-1975 1972-1975 (Box 1)
- Family Housing Council: Tom Whitman President for 1970-1971 1965-1976, n.d., 2 folders (Box 1)
- Housing Information 1973-1976 (Box 1)
- List of Residents 1969-1979 (Box 2)
- Parking and Road Safety Problems 1964-1975 (Box 2)
- Party Information 1965 (Box 2)
- Rule Violations 1968-1975 (Box 2)
- University Family Housing Association Newsletters 1967-1977 (Box 2)